good morning everyone it is a lovely
cool day and I'm off to town to run some
errands most important of which is to
find a new book to read which is an
absolute
[Music]
emergency I go into town regularly since
I frequent the post office things get
busy during tourist season so I tend to
get up very early in the morning and
avoid the crowds however comparatively
few people live here full-time I'm
grateful for this since it is very
important to me to be involved in my
community even if it's a small one I
found that as someone who prefers more
quiet living it gives me great joy to
spend time in town and then be able to
go home to a more peaceful Haven when I
feel like it I did this in the city too
and prioritized having a peaceful space
to go home to after work
[Music]
this town is right next to a river so it
is wonderful to be able to walk around
on a hot day and then go down to the
water to cool off and
read as with many beautiful places this
area struggles with having many vacation
homes that are empty most of the year so
it can be difficult to find places to
rent thankfully there are many young
people who've gotten creative and found
ways to live and work here full-time
sometimes living off grid or fixing up
old houses it's definitely useful to be
handy here as help can be in short
supply my boyfriend used to work in
construction and is now a surveyor and
I've enjoyed the benefits of his
carpentry skills and experience with
home repairs many
times of course my favorite place in my
town is my bookstore it always brings me
back to my time as a book seller
there's so much magic in places like
these I always think about the way the
shells are just full of stories waiting
to be discovered I've recently been
reading a lot of fantasy and fairy tales
I love to get lost in here for
[Music]
hours if there is only one piece of
advice I would ever give someone trying
to find a new place to live is to be
very patient in my experience is that
with an open heart the right home has a
way of finding you if only you slowly
work towards your goals and let life
guide you to the right place at the
right time of course if moving to a new
location isn't practical which is
understandable I truly believe that an
abundant and peaceful home life can only
be created not
found for example my mother researched
homes throughout the decades my father
was in the military it took her nearly
30 years she wanted to find an
affordable place with in her budget and
at long last she found her dream home
she couldn't be happier saying that the
adventure that brought her here made her
far more ready and grateful for it I've
taken inspiration from her and know
someday I will have my own home and will
enjoy waiting for it as I put aside a
little bit every month
[Music]
anyway I hope you all have a lovely day
next week I will share with you the only
other part of my town that I love almost
as much as the bookstore so I will see
you soon
[Music]
it's
ni
[Music]
than